(Penny:)Look, Amy, all you need to know
is you are my friend.
l don't wanna lose you out of my life.
(Amy:)I'm sorry, I'm just having trouble
believing you right now.
- Grab your hammer.
- No, damage is done.
Okay, look, I didn't wanna say this...
(Penny:)...but the real reason
l took the painting down...
(Penny:)...was because it made Bernadette
very jealous.
(Amy:)Oh, my goodness.
(Amy:)How could I have not seen that?
(Amy:)The painting is a constant reminder
that of the three of us...
(Amy:)...she is the least cool.
Yeah, that's what it is, so...
- You have such a good heart.
- Oh. I try.
(Penny:)- Come on.
- Well, where are we going?
We're gonna put this back up.
(Penny:)What about Bernadette?
(Amy:)Oh, screw her. She's just lucky
we let her hang out with us.